# Robert Thaiyah Kibue

56449, 00200

📱 0728086589 | 🗷 bobthaiyah@gmail.com | 🌴 https://robert-thaiyah.vercel.app/ | 🖸 github.com/Robert-Thaiyah | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/robert-thaiyah

# Personal Profile

A Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology graduate student who was enrolled in the Diploma in Information Technology program. Dedicated to software engineering, and specialising in Email and front-end web development. Searching mostly for IT Support, Email and Front-end Development positions.

## Education

#### Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology

Juja, Kenya

Diploma in Information Technology

Jan 2019 - Dec 2022

- · Graduated with Distinction
- Courses: Principles of Computer Support and Maintenance, Software Engineering, Web Development, Database Management Systems, Network Design and Maintenance, Digital Photography and Video Editing, Mobile Computing, Learning Skill through Course Mandated Projects.

#### **Kenya Methodist University**

Meru, Kenya

Sep 2013 - Sep 2017

Bachelor in Medicine and Bachelor in Surgery

Performed fours years of study in pursuit of Bachelor's before exiting program

#### Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology

Juja, Kenya

Cisco Certified Network Associate(CCNA)

Sept 2018 - Sept 2019

- · Passed with Certificate
- Courses: Network Fundamentals, IP Connectivity, Network Access, Security Fundamentals.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### Jomo Kenyatta University Hospital

Juja, Kenya

IT Support Intern

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- · Collaborated with a four-person team to implement and test the newly developed Hospital Management System
- Trained the staff to use the newly developed system, logged any errors that arose from the system, and solved issues that arose from user accounts.
- Liaised with all the department within the hospital to assist with any issues that arose during normal operating hours. Complex issues were logged and raised to the Supervisor.
- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Hardware and Software Support, Windows 10 Support, Network Support and Troubleshooting.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills, Staff Training.

Real-biz Digital Solutions

Nairobi, Kenya

Graphic Design Intern

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

- Collaborated with Supervisor to create amazing websites using the WordPress Platform.
- Data-mined and Reversed Engineered Websites as per the Supervisor's request.
- Created amazing Mock-ups and Wire-frames using Adobe XD and Figma platforms.
- Technical Skills: WordPress, Wire-framing, Data-mining, Reverse Engineering, Mock-up Design.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

#### **Aga Khan University Hospital**

Nairobi, Kenya

Pediatrics Intern Apr 2017 - May 2017

- Gathered patient's history, conducted examinations, suggested clinical diagnosis and follow-up treatment protocols
- · Data-entry of all patients records into the hospital management system and the physical patient file during ward rotations
- Rotated between various Pediatric Departments i.e Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, Pediatric Intensive Care Unit, Pediatric Private Wing and Outpatient Pediatric Wing.
- Technical Skills: Data Entry, Client-Patient Confidentiality, Diagnostic Skills.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

# Personal Projects \_\_\_\_\_

July 25, 2023

**Robert Kibue Personal Portfolio** 

Nairobi, Kenya

Robert Kibue May 2023 - July 2023

- This is my personal Portfolio which demonstrates my skills in Front-end Technologies. Live-site is in the CV Header, together with relevant links.
- Additional Projects are located in my website homepage.
- Technical Skills: HTML, Tailwind CSS, React.
- GitHub Repository: Robert Kibue
- Live-Site: Robert Kibue Personal Portfolio

#### **Denti Dental Landing Page**

Nairobi, Kenya

Robert Kibue Jan 2023 - Feb 2023

- This is a landing page for a fictional dental hospital called Denti.
- The project was recreated from an existing project found on Dribbble. Project Author is Webflix and can be found at Webflix Denti Landing Page.
- Technical Skills: HTML, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript.
- GitHub Repository: Denti Dental.
- · Live-Site: Denti Dental Landing Page.

#### **Gentium Agency Landing Page**

Nairobi. Kenva

Robert Kibue

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

- This is a landing page for a fictional digital agency called Gentium
- · The project was recreated from an existing project found on Dribbble. Project Author is UniStudio and can be found at UniStudio Gentium Agency.
- Technical Skills: HTML, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript.
- GitHub Repository: Gentium Agency
- · Live-Site: Gentium Agency Landing Page

# Skills\_

**Web Development** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, React.

Front-end Development React, Bootstrap.

Miscellaneous Microsoft Office, Git, UI/UX Design, Network Support and Troubleshooting, Hardware Support and Troubleshooting.

**Soft Skills** Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Customer Support

## Interests

I love cooking. I am an expert in most Kenyan-style cooking, enjoy baking and making my own pizza.

**Video Games** I always had the gaming gene. I mostly play on my phone and occasionally on my PC.

**Swimming** I started swimming when I was 12. Going through submerged things while holding my breath was the most exciting part.

Volleyball I always love playing volleyball as a part-time sport, specifically the Setter and Lobero positions.

Arts I am always fascinated by the different art styles people have. I often visit plays and museums when the opportunity arises.